# Ashwini Wakchaure

# PG Diploma in Advanced Computing

Self-motivated professional with more than three years of experience in a manufacturing environment. Seeking a career opportunity in a software company as a Full Stack Developer where I can use my extensive knowledge of programming languages and frameworks to develop efficient web applications.



ashwakchaure@gmail.com



9403918337



Pune, India



linkedin.com/in/ashwiniwakchaure-6a5b65161



github.com/ashwiniwakchaur e7777

# **SKILLS**

NODE.JS

REACT. IS

IAVASCRIPT

EXPRESS.JS

MYSQL

HTML

MONGO DB

CSS

# **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Full Professional Proficiency

#### Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

#### Marathi

Full Professional Proficiency

# **INTERESTS**

Listening music

Reading

Travelling

## **EDUCATION**

# **Post Graduation Diploma in Advanced Computing**

Centre for Development of Advanced Computing

09/2022 - 03/2023

Project

Project - Hospital Management System

# **Bachelors in Mechanical Engineering**

Sinhagad Academy of Engineering

06/2015 - 06/2018

## MY PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

https://ashwiniwakchaure.netlify.app/

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Process Automation Specialist**

#### Infosys BPM Ltd

11/2021 - 06/2022

Work and responsibilities

Worked on Generation of Purchase Orders & timely issuance of POs to Vendors, follow-up for order confirmation, and co-ordination for on-time payment to suppliers

CCEE: A Grade

75.06%

Pune

Pune

- Handled all P2P activities and handles the PO related queries
- Handled overseas Suppliers, tracking & maintaining system

#### **Purchase Executive**

## Tata Motors Ltd

12/2018 - 11/2021

Work and responsibilities

Interpreted engineering drawings, part lists and volume of materials to make informed

- Interpreted engineering drawings, part lists and volume of materials to make informed purchase decisions
- Analyzed vendors and suppliers to select the most suitable to deliver high-quality products at competitive pricing
- Implemented alternate sourcing of static suppliers through sourcing with another suppliers
- Developed, implemented, and drove purchase strategies to meet cost savings targets, planned supplier's capacity to meet production requirements
- Liaised with vendors and suppliers on delivery schedule to achieve on-time delivery, raw material indexing

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Received applause for early self enablement

Infosys BPM Ltd

Received appreciation and kudos for driving execution

Tata Motors Ltd